威尔 · 森塔斯: 我认为值得从人们开始谈论一些话题
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I think it is worth
starting off people with some words about
这个同步会把我们带到哪里。
where this a sync is gonna take us.
我们会兑现承诺。
Promises we're gonna cover promises.
如果你看到了某个困难的部分，那么你就会记得它是,
If you've seen v one of hard parts,
then you remember that it's,
我认为，我们有传统的 ES5回调模式。
we got, I think,
to the traditional ES5 callback model.
我们看到回调队列是这样的。
And we saw the callback queue
is all these sort of pieces.
在 ES6中，可能最重要的附加特性是承诺。
In ES6, probably the most significant
additional feature was promises.
所以他们不会和回收模式有根本的不同。
Under the hood, so they're not going to be
radically different to the callback model.
然后我们将会看到我认为是什么使得 JavaScript 成为最重要的特性
Then we're gonna see the key feature of
what I think makes JavaScript the most
强大而通俗的语言。
powerful and popular language.
在网络世界中，这是一个同步性。
A certainly in the web world,
and that is it's a synchronicity.
这就是使动态 web 应用成为可能的原因。
This is what makes dynamic
web applications possible.
这就意味着当你点击大量松弛的表情符号时。
This is what means that when you're
clicking lots of slack emoji responses.
我们还能做什么？
What else would we do?
当你点击那些松弛的表情符号时,
When you're clicking all
those slack emoji responses,
并不是所有的数据都在你本地电脑上更新。
they're not all being updated on
your local machine on your computer.
这些都是通过互联网发送的,
It's so
that's all being sent over the internet,
千里之外回来确认
thousands of miles away
coming back confirming and
然后以某种方式同时发生在一种单线程语言中。
then somehow all happening simultaneously
in a single threaded language.
这可能已经让你停下来思考事件循环
Already that might give you pause for
thought of the event loop which is gonna
结果发现这是 Joshua 发球的方式
turn out to be Joshua's way of
teeing up what's going to run and
他在跑什么，接下来要跑什么。
what he's running and
what's going to run next.
然后一些非常有趣的，这些微任务队列，我想大声说出来
And then some really interesting these the
micro task queue that I wanna shout out
杰克 · 阿奇博尔德，我们的英国朋友,
Jake Archibald, our fellow British friend,
他是谈论市场的人之一
who is one of the people who talked
about the market ask you and
谁喜欢你和网页浏览器的功能真的很重要。
it really important who likes you and
the web browser features.
但我们又回到了起点。
But we're back where we started.
我们要重新回到马鞍上
We are going to get back in the saddle so
通过提醒自己乔布斯会如何宽恕常规代码来说话。
to speak by reminding ourselves how
jobs would excuse regular code.
好了，开始了，各位。
Okay, here we go, people.
我们回来了。
We're back.
一号线到凯拉一号线我们在这里做什么？
So line one is over to Kayla line one,
what are we doing here?
请记住，运行代码有两部分，分别逐行和逐行检查
Remember there's two parts running
code going through it line by line and
边走边存东西。
saving stuff as we go.
第一行 Kayla 我们在第一行做什么？
So Kayla, the line one, what are we
doing in our very first line here?
我们在定义恒定标准
&gt;&gt; Kayla: We're defining constant norm and
将值设置为3
setting the value to three
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful where's that
被拯救？
being saved?
数据保存在哪里？
Where's that data being saved?
在全球记忆中。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: In global memory.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic.
所以 norm 在整体内存中被赋值为3美。
So norm is assigned a value of
3 in global memory beautiful.
让我们看看托德，下一行我们要做什么？
Let's go over to Todd,
what are we doing Todd in the next line?
托德: 我们定义的函数乘以2。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Our defined
function multiplied by two.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了，也就是说我们接受了它的标签,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic, and
that is to say we're taking its label,
这是它的标识符，然后把包括参数在内的所有代码
that's its identifier, and then taking all
the code of it including the parameter as
一个占位符，用来填充数据，最后我们用这个代码。
a placeholder, that's gonna be filled in
with data and we end up using this code.
在使用此代码时使用值排序，并且
Sort of with a value in using this code,
and
我们一次性全部保留下来，太棒了。
we are saving it all in one go, fantastic.
下一行。
Next line.
让我们把马特留在左手边。
Let us have Matt left hand side.
Matt: 你要在全局内存中定义常量输出。
&gt;&gt; Matt: You are gonna define
the constant output in the global memory.
威尔 · 森特斯: 美丽的每个人在这一点上都是如此的专业。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful
everybody is so pro at this point.
非常好。
It is very nice.
定义内存的常量输出。
Define the constant output of memory.
马特，我要在那个恒定输出中存储什么？
Matt, what am I gonna store
in that constant output?
马特: 乘以二的结果。
&gt;&gt; Matt: The result of multiplied by two.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 编码的结果乘以二。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The result
of coding multiplied by two.
很漂亮，那么现在，各位，是吗？
Beautiful, so for now, everybody it is?
观众: 未初始化。
&gt;&gt; Audience: Uninitialized.
威尔 · 森特斯: 非常好，特别照顾。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice,
taken care of specially.
好了，我们不要用乘以2来调用
All right, so
let's not get calling multiply by 2
输入的范数是值，3，它的输出,
with the input of norm which is the value,
3, its output,
它的返回值将被存储到输出中。
it's returned value is going
to be stored into outputs.
我们要创造一个全新的世界吗？
And we're gonna create,
everybody, a brand new?
观众: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Audience: Execution context.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我也觉得很棒。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic
in line with me as well.
好了。
There we go.
安德鲁，我们去民间。
And Andrew we go folk.
是的，形状很好。
Yeah, very nicely shaped.
它就在那里，我们的第一件事就是进入它的本地记忆
There it is and
into its local memory our first thing
存储为分配给哪个参数名的值3，Jeff？
stored as a value three assigned
to what parameter name, Jeff?
杰夫: 输入号码。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Input number.
威尔 · 句子: 输入数字，是的，民众。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Input number, yes folk.
这是输入的数字，然后丹通过函数的主体告诉我
There it is input number then Dan told
me through the body of the function
阿丹: 我们在定义恒定的结果。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We are defining constant result.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 结果丹: 我们给
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Results
&gt;&gt; Dan: And we're assigning the value of
输入数乘以2？
input number multiplied by 2
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is?
然后我们做什么？
&gt;&gt; Dan: 6
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And then we do what?
丹: 我们返回指定的值
Dan
&gt;&gt; Dan: We return out the value assigned
来标记结果。
to label result.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 说得很好，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nicely put,
exactly.
然后加入全局常量，输出，就是这个，完美。
And adding comes into the global constant,
output, there it is, perfect.
各位，我想说的是,
People, I wanna just talk about,
不过，看看执行的过程。
though, look at the journey
of the thread of execution.
从现在开始我要用绿色。
I'm gonna do in green from now on.
当我们点到这条线时，乘以2。
When we hit this line here,
the of multiply by two.
我们的执行线程，记住，这是我们运行代码所需要的一半。
Our thread of execution, remember, that's
the half of what we need to run code.
我们需要运行代码的能力，就像这个左边这样,
We need the ability to run code,
sort of this left-hand side here,
还有储存东西的能力，这两个部分。
and the ability to store stuff,
those two parts.
当我们开始运行 multiply by 2时。
When we started running multiply by2.
所以我们开始运行我们的代码，我们的执行线程正在崩溃。
So we started running our code,
our thread of execution was going down.
它按下标签输出，然后运行更多的代码。
It hit label output, and
then go run some more code.
所以我们的执行线程必须用来运行这个函数的代码。
So our thread of execution had to be
used to run the code of that function.
我们进入它，直到我们完成这个函数,
Into it we went and
until we finished inside this function,
我们允许进入下一行代码和全局代码？
where we allow to move on to
the next line of code and global?
不，因为 JavaScript 是一种同步语言,
No, because JavaScript is
a synchronous language,
是一种同步语言，它意味着我们要做每一行,
JavaScript is a synchronous language
that means we do each line,
我们完成它，当我们完成，我们去下一行，好吗。
we finish it,
when we finish that we go next line, okay.
所以我们开始，我们做了里面的所有代码
So into we went and
we did all the code inside of it and
直到我们完成它，我们没有退出，到下一行。
until we finished with it,
we did not exit out to the next line.
当我们这样做的时候，我们关闭了这个执行环境，然后继续前进。
And when we did, at that point we closed
this execution context and we moved on.
然后我们在全球的下一行。
And then we hit our next line in global.
但是你可以想象我们运行代码的语言,
But you could imagine the language
where we would have run our code,
我们的线程会被乘以2运行它
our thread would have gone into
multiplied by two run it and
我们会在 global 继续我们的执行线程。
we'd have continued our thread
of execution in global.
但不是在 JavaScript 中。
But not in JavaScript.
在 JavaScript 中，如果我们有一行代码要做，我们就必须去做。
In JavaScript, if we have a line
of code to do, we have to do it.
这是我们唯一能做的代码行
It's the only line of code we can do and
我们必须完成它，然后才能进入下一行，好吗？
we had to finish on it before
we move to the next line, okay?
威尔 · 森特斯: 你可能已经在想，坚持住,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Already you
might be thinking hold on,
如果那条线是条很慢的线呢？
what if that line is a really slow line?
假设这条线可能是在和 Twitter 对话,
Suppose that lines a line that
might be speaking to Twitter,
在互联网上的速度真的很慢。
over the Internet really slowly.
好的，下一行是声明新的输出。
All right,
next line we hit is declaring new output.
后面的亚当，我们要怎么做才能得到我们的价值
Adam in the back, what are we gonna
do in order to get our value or
为了完成这行代码，最后一行代码,
in order to finish this line of code,
the final line of coding,
我们该怎么办？
what do we gotta go and do?
这最后一句话告诉我们要做什么？
What is this final line telling us to do?
声明新的输出。
Declare new output.
亚当: 把它分配给求值，然后乘以二，再乘以十。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Assign it to evaluation and
multiply by two with an input of ten.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 绝对的，所以，这意味着我们得走了
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely,
so, that means we gotta go and
执行这个函数。
execute this function.
快速地为它创建一个新的执行上下文
Create a new execution context for
it very quickly
创建一个新的执行上下文进入它，我们要去
create a new execution context
into it we're gonna go and
在本地内存中，我们会有输入号码,
in local memory,
we are going to have input number,
分配给10个结果，我们知道这个权利？
assigned to 10 result, we know this right?
结果将是20，返回的值将结果输出到新的输出。
Result will be 20 and the return of
value result out into new output.
我们的执行线程，我们唯一的执行线程，唯一的执行线程
Our thread of execution, our single
thread of execution, the single do one
在这里的时候，我们可以运行更多的代码吗？
thing at a time while inside of here,
can we be running any further code?
没有，等我们做完了我们就可以出来了。
No, and when we're finished
with that we can come out.